▍2026 美网 男单第一轮
孟菲尔斯 2-6 6-1 6-2 6-0 巴列霍 · 赛后场上采访
Well, Gaël, the show goes on.
加埃尔 好戏还在继续
Here in New York.
就在纽约
What a performance.
多精彩的表现
What a match. You're
多精彩的一场球
through to the second round,
你晋级第二轮了
and you've done it in style.
而且赢得很漂亮
Good evening, New York.
晚上好 纽约
Um Uh
嗯
that was that was definitely very special.
这真的 真的很特别
Play the day of my 40th birthday
在四十岁生日这天打球
is a special.
很特别
You guys made it like incredible,
你们让这一切好得不可思议
you know?
你们知道吗
I mean Hey.
我是说 嘿
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
Have a good one.
祝你们愉快
Wow, what a way
哇 这个庆祝方式
to celebrate your 40th birthday.
来过你的四十岁生日
This is your 18th US Open.
这是你第十八次打美网
And listen,
还有
you're through to the second round.
你晋级第二轮了
How You have a special relationship
你和这里的观众
with the crowd here in New York.
有一种特别的关系
There's no doubt about it.
这一点毫无疑问
How special is it for you
对你来说有多特别
to play another match here in New York?
能在纽约再打一场球？
You know, it's it's very special.
你知道 这非常特别
You guys always make it like you
你们总能让这里
know, electric, amazing.
像通了电一样 太棒了
The atmosphere is unbelievable.
这里的气氛难以置信
I feel great here, and always you know,
我在这里感觉很好
I try to put great tennis,
我想打出好网球
but a great show, and you guys are rock,
也想给一场好表演 你们最棒
so let's keep it up for the second one.
第二轮我们继续
And just finally, Gaël,
最后一个问题 加埃尔
we've already spoken
我们已经聊过
about it being your 40th birthday,
今天是你的四十岁生日
so happy birthday again.
再祝你生日快乐
Your wife, Elina, is of course watching
你太太斯维托丽娜
in the crowd.
当然就在看台上
You guys have already played mixed
你们俩已经一起
doubles together, but I wanted to ask,
打过混双了 但我想问
has she got your birthday present yet?
她送你生日礼物了吗？
And if so, can you reveal to us what it was?
送了的话 能说说是什么吗？
Actually, I mean I think she's
其实 我想她
playing tomorrow, so it's great effort
明天还有比赛
for her to to stay here.
能留下来对她很不容易
So, yes, she did.
所以 是的 她送了
It was an amazing gift.
是一份很棒的礼物
If she allowed me to say it,
如果她允许我说的话
she she offered me a great watch
她送了我一块很棒的表
for my 40th.
为我的四十岁
There you go.
就是这样